

# Hossein YousefpourEstahbanati

Flutter Developer

Example Email: <a href="mailto:h.yusefpour@gmail.com">h.yusefpour@gmail.com</a>
<a href="mailto:h.yusefpour@gmail.com">h.yusefpour@gmailto:h.yusefpour@gmail.com</a>
<a href="mailto:h.yusefpour@gmailto:

in Linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/gabrimatic

Github: https://github.com/gabrimatic

#### **SUMMARY**

Thanks to my great interest in smartphones, I learned Java and Kotlin languages to develop applications for Android devices when I was 14. In 2019, I learned to work with Flutter, and now it's more than four years that I have been developing apps for Android, iOS, Web, and Desktop platforms. At the beginning of 2021, I found my subsequent interest in the Web3 world! And now, I'm also developing decentralized apps (like crypto wallets) with Flutter.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Enpal GmbH**, Berlin, Germany — Flutter Developer

March 2022 - September 2022

Enpal is the first green Unicorn in Germany and the fastest-growing company located at the intersection of green energy and technology. Enpal leases photovoltaics and the tech ecosystem around them to end consumers monthly to equip one million households with clean energy by 2030.

# Welf Group GmbH, Hannover, Germany — Flutter Developer

March 2022 - September 2022

As a remote employee of the Flutter team, I was in charge of developing the Carepoint Healthcare app connecting it to the Firebase services and publishing the Aloga Auction App to AppStore.

### **Hashverse**, Amsterdam, Netherlands — Flutter dApps Developer

February 2022 - August 2022

I was the head of the Flutter team developing Hashverse Crypto Wallet dApp to manage Tokens, NFTs, Topics, Files, etc., powered by Hedera Hashgraph.

I also developed the first Hedera Dart SDK using gRPC APIs to connect Dart-based projects (like Flutter) to the Hedera Hashgraph network.

#### **SKILLS**

# Programing

- Flutter
- Dart
- Web3 Apps (dApps)
- Android (Java/Kotlin)

# Development

- o SQL & No-SQL
- o BLoC
- o REST
- o gRPC
- o Git
- Firebase
- Socket programming
- AppStore & GooglePlay
- o CI/CD

## Soft Skills

- o Fast/Self Learner
- Problem Solver
- o Time Management
- Self Management
- Motivated
- Mind-mapping
- Discipline
- Passionate
- Patience

#### **FIELDS OF INTEREST**

- Mobile Apps Development
- Web3 Development
- Finding Solutions

# DuckDuckGoose, Delft, Netherlands — Mobile Engineer

June 2022 - July 2022

As a freelancer, I set up a mobile pipeline with specific requirements to accelerate the company's deepfake penetration test processes on different Android apps. I helped the development team to manage to come up with a new design.

### **Medis Holding,** Shiraz, Iran — Flutter Developer

April 2020 - March 2022

In Medis, We developed projects using **Flutter** for mobile and web platforms and published them on Google Play, AppStore, and web hosts.

As a part of the Flutter App and Web team, I developed <u>Alobodo</u>, <u>Wand</u>, <u>Elimedi</u>, and <u>Dorisbank</u> projects with Flutter for mobile and web platforms.

We implemented Firebase cloud messaging for sending in-app notifications And also real-time chat services using socket programming.

# **Azhman Engineers**, Shiraz, Iran — Android and Flutter Developer

May 2018 - April 2020

As a mobile engineer at Azhman Engineers company, I developed its first internal mobile app using the Flutter framework AghighMobile.

I also developed the P-Barg digital bookstore Android app using Kotlin language.

## **Utab Pars**, Shiraz, Iran — Junior Android Developer

October 2018 - August 2019

Participated as a freelance junior Android developer in projects (Kifduzak and SinaMobile insurance). I mostly used **Java** in my development.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Zand Higher Education Institute**, Shiraz, Iran — Associate Degree

In Computer Software

2017 - 2021

# **Shohada Technical High School**, Shiraz, Iran — Diploma Degree

In Computer Science

2014 - 2016

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### Persian

Native

#### **English**

Professional working proficiency

#### German

Elementary proficiency